There will be no bargain.
I will not give up
my favorite decoration.
I like Captain Solo where he is.
Ah! Do that again!
I have come for the
bounty on this Wookiee.
At last we have the mighty Chewbacca.
I want fifty thousand. No less.
This bounty hunter is my kind of
scum, fearless and inventive.
It's too late for that, Solo.
You may have been a good smuggler...
...but now you're Bantha fodder.
Take him away.
Bring her to me.
I'm sure.
I told you not to admit him.
He must be allowed to speak.
You weak-minded fool!
He's using an old Jedi mind trick.
Your mind powers will
not work on me, boy.
There will be no bargain, young Jedi.
I shall enjoy watching you die.
Bring me Solo and the Wookiee.
They will all suffer for this outrage.
Soon you will learn to appreciate me.
Move him into position.
Put him in.